Nan Chun Wang, Front end Web Developer

 $5\ Floors, No.\ 70, Wulang\ St, West\ District,\ Taichung,\ 403,\ Taiwan, (+886)\ 987046741,\ mark 36949@gmail.com$

LINKS	GitHub, LinkedIn Hello, I am Mark Wang, a Fronted-End Web developer in Chunghwa Telecom Co., Ltd. Taiwan. I'm in charge of redesigning the view of website, improving user experience and maintaining the features. I hold a bachelor's degree with a major in Computer Science which was awarded to me by National Central University in Taoyuan in 2018. After graduated, I studied in Institute of Network Learning Technology .		
PROFILE			
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY			
Feb 2021 — Present	Front-End Web Developer , Chungh	wa Telecom Co., Ltd.	Taipei
	Mainly worked on User Interface (UI) redesign & developed Front-End Web based on Vue .		
	Provided effective troubleshooting and remediation for web applications.		
Sep 2018 — Jun 2020	Research Study Assistant, Institute of Technology	of Network Learning	Taoyuan
	Online Learning Platform (<u>CoSci</u>)		
	Designed, developed, and modified research e	xperiments alongside teams of researchers.	
EDUCATION			
Sep 2018 — Jun 2020	Master's degree, Institute of Networ National Central University	k Learning Technology,	Taoyuan, Taiwan
	Interactive Technology and Learning Lab, advised by Prof. Chen-Chung Liu.		
	Graduate thesis: "The analysis of the effect of mutual attention awareness through the mouse cursor on online collaborative learning"		
Sep 2014 — Jun 2018	Bachelor's degree, Science in Computer Science and Information Taoyuan, Taiwan Engineering , National Central University		
	Leader of Basketball Team of Computer Science Department at NCU.		
	Member of Graduate Student Association at NCU.		
	Member of Student Association of Computer Science Department at NCU.		
SKILLS	Vue	Bootstrap 4	
	JavaScript	Java	
	HTML & CSS	Spring Boot	
PROJECTS			
Jan 2019 — May 2020	Web-based Simulation (Dual Eye-Tracking Analysis)		
	Implemented eye-tracking analysis tool by MATLAB CRP and CRQA tool.		
	Developed real-time collaborative simulation by utilizing RK4 and Socket Programming.		
	Created and designed server database using MongoDB for data analyzing.		
Oct 2017	Meichu Hackthon		
	Collaborated with 2 friends to build up keyboard application.		
Oct 2019	Meichu Hackthon		
	Designed website layout and established principles.		
	Organized 3 members into different workflow.		